Finding Aid for Michael Daugherty papers, 1973-2013
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Teaching Materials
  The Teaching Materials include notes, ideas, and materials collected from various lectures and workshops that Daugherty held, or assisted with.
  - College Music Society Annual Meeting 1985 (Box 41)
  - Lectures undated
    - Elvis undated (Box 41)
    - Superman undated (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous Notes and Ideas 1982-2012 (Box 41)
  - Summer Workshop -- Oberlin 1989-1991 (Box 41)
- Miscellaneous
  The Miscellaneous series includes materials Daugherty used to prepare playing synthesizers for a silent film, a musical analysis of Daugherty's Bizzaro, and several promotional shirts.
  - Michael Daugherty: Bizzaro by Karen Fannin, 2000 (Box 41)
    (musical analysis)
  - Silent Film Information 1984-1991 (Box 41)
    (used to prepare playing synthesizers for a silent film)
  - Promotional Shirts (Box 42)